<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>book on /home/dhruv-joshi</title>
    <link>https://thepoetdj.github.io/tags/book/</link>
    <description>Recent content in book on /home/dhruv-joshi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018-{year} &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/thepoetdj&#34;&gt;Dhruv Joshi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;:: Favicon made by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.deviantart.com/bakacowdesu&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;bakacowdesu&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thepoetdj.github.io/tags/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Became a Published Author with &#34;Whispering Solitude&#34;</title>
      <link>https://thepoetdj.github.io/posts/getting-published-with-whispering-solitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepoetdj.github.io/posts/getting-published-with-whispering-solitude/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Did you know that every story has its own taste &amp;amp; color? Some stories are between black &amp;amp; white, some are bright gold and, some are just old yellow. The &amp;lsquo;Whispering Solitude&amp;rsquo; is created to celebrate the blue stories of the imaginations running wild. One of those wild, yet colorful imaginations, is penned down by me!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Did you know that every story has its own taste &amp;amp; color? Some stories are between black &amp;amp; white, some are bright gold and, some are just old yellow. The &amp;lsquo;Whispering Solitude&amp;rsquo; is created to celebrate the blue stories of the imaginations running wild. One of those wild, yet colorful imaginations, is penned down by me!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://thepoetdj.github.io/images/book_cover.jpg&#34;  alt=&#34;Whispering Solitude book cover&#34;   /&gt;
    
      &lt;figcaption class=&#34;center&#34; &gt;Title&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
  &lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Since we are talking about an anthology book here, this might be the right time to tell you what an anthology is before we move forward. An &lt;strong&gt;anthology&lt;/strong&gt;, in a nutshell, is a collection of short stories, poems, songs or even plays. Also, the compilation of those literary works can either be by the same or different authors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The book we are talking about&amp;ndash;Whispering Solitude&amp;ndash;is an anthology of short stories by various authors. Every author had complete freedom over choosing a suitable genre for their story that, when compiled together, resulted in an anthology filled with rich and colorful stories, each full of surprises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the book is closing on its release date, let&amp;rsquo;s chat with one of the team members behind this project to answer some of the common questions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tell us a few words on &amp;lsquo;Whispering Solitude&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whispering Solitude is a book where every single writer has let loose their imagination to create some very exciting and memorable stories. It&amp;rsquo;s a roller coaster of different heights I tell you. The idea to support and motivate new budding writers to reach a new heights was already looming in our minds. Admin Subathra was the first to come up with the idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What does the title mean?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The name was the result of our struggling to come up with someting that was new and reflected us all, different voices of creators all at once. The meaning is better explained at the back cover - find the color of your story!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who are the authors?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every author is novice in a sense or another but professional for their crave of presenting something new.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Which genres will be there?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh you open this book with an expectation and you are in for a surprise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This being your first anthology, how was the overall experience of your team and the authors.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The experience was a bliss and fun but truth be told, no writer can experience the joy they feel while a reader picks up their book to read. Every budding writer did their part with such grace, we had trouble selecting the final count.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When can we expect it released?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully, by mid october.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Any future plans you would like to share with us?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Future plans are already in motion. Shortly we&amp;rsquo;ll begin working on our next anthology, which will be a collection of quotes and poems. Stay tuned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Our community, Writer&amp;rsquo;s Arcadia is by the authors &amp;amp; for the authors. So get ready for a journey filled with ups &amp;amp; awws, as each and every writer has let loose the bounds of creativity for you. Read up and know the color of your story.&lt;/em&gt; - team &lt;strong&gt;Writer&amp;rsquo;s Arcadia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit:&lt;/strong&gt; The book is finally out on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.in/dp/B07K1WCYPY&#34;&gt;amazon&lt;/a&gt;. Go grab a copy of yours.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
